stylefeeder.com 2011-05-29

# StyleFeeder Privacy Policy

  |  |  |   |    
**PRIVACY NOTICE** |    
  
**Table of Contents** |    
* The Information We Collect
* How We Use the Information 
* Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors
* Privacy Options
* Cookies
* Our Commitment to Security
* How You can Access or Correct Information
* Special Note for Parents
* Changes to this Notice
* How to Contact Us
| 

European Union Privacy Information   
Canada Privacy Information

|    
  
This is the Privacy Policy for the United States of America which applies to you if you live outside the European Union or Canada. 

Thank you for visiting StyleFeeder, a site within the network of sites of Time Inc. and its subsidiaries, each of which have adopted this Privacy Notice. Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used by Time Inc. and its subsidiaries. [Click here](http://www.timeinc.net/subs/privacy/bus_units.html) for a list of the sites of Time Inc. and its subsidiaries which are governed by this Privacy Notice. 

|    
  
**The Information We Collect**  
Through Time Inc. publications, websites and other media, you can order publications and products, and engage in various activities like entering contests or sweepstakes, playing games, taking quizzes, voting in polls or otherwise expressing an opinion, subscribing to one of our services, such as newsletters, or participating in one of our online forums or communities. Your personally identifiable information may be required to engage in these activities as well as to receive products and services that you may have requested. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages and elsewhere include but are not limited to: name, address, gender, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number and credit or debit card information. 

We may also collect information about your personal or professional interests and use of or opinions about various products, programs and services. For instance, we may ask you to identify your job or industry to qualify you for free business magazines. 

At some Time Inc. sites and through certain promotions, you can submit information about other people. For example, you might submit a person's name, mailing and/or e-mail address to send a gift or electronic greeting card. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at these pages include: recipient's name, address, e-mail address and telephone number. 

We may also collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit our web pages or use our applications, such as the type of browser and operating system you are using, your IP Address and your Internet service provider, and location-based information. 

| back to top  
  
**How We Use the Information**  
We may use the information you provide about yourself or others to fulfill requests for our publications, products or services, to respond to inquiries about offerings and to offer other products, programs or services that may be of interest. 

We may combine information we receive with outside records and share such information with third parties to enhance our ability to market to you those products or services that may be of interest to you. 

We may disclose personally identifiable information to third parties whose practices are not covered by this privacy statement (e.g., other marketers, magazine publishers, retailers, participatory databases and non-profit organizations) that want to market products or services to you. 

When you request a magazine, service or other product, we will forward the information you give us to the publisher or provider for fulfillment. They may contact you with special offers of possible interest. 

We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when you have won one of our contests or sweepstakes, or when we make changes to subscriber agreements, to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter or to contact you about your account. 

If you choose to submit content (e.g., a "letter to our editors" or an online review), we may publish your name, screen name and other information you have provided to us. 

The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs or services. 

We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our publications and websites, and to enable us to customize your Internet experience. We also may use this information to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs or services. 

We will disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request. 

Agents and contractors of Time Inc. that have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for Time Inc. 

We may transfer your personally identifiable information to other Time Inc. offices for internal management and administrative purposes. Your personal data will be transferred to other Time Inc. offices where necessary for the performance or conclusion of our contractual obligations to you or for your benefit. Transfers of personally identifiable information may also be made where necessary for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims. 

Please note that if Time Inc. or any of its subsidiaries or lines of business is sold or otherwise disposed of, including through merger of, consolidation or sale of assets, the relevant customer database, including personally identifiable information we may possess about you, may, in whole or in part, be sold, disposed of, transferred or otherwise disclosed as part of that transaction. 

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice. Inadvertent disclosures may result, for example, when third parties misrepresent their identities in asking the site for access to personally identifiable information about themselves for purposes of correcting possible factual errors in the data. 

|    
  
**Privacy Options**  
If you prefer not to receive traditional mail or other off-line promotions from this or any other Time Inc. property or any companies not owned by Time Inc., please click here. |    
  
If you prefer not to receive e-mail marketing from this or any other Time Inc. property or any companies not owned by Time Inc., please click here. 

Time Inc. sites will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses. 

| back to top  
  
**Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors**  
Some of our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. You should consult the other sites' privacy notices, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. 

Time Inc. sites sometimes may offer contests, sweepstakes, promotions, editorial features or other activities or offerings that are sponsored or co-sponsored by or presented with identified third parties. By virtue of your participation in such activities or offerings, your IP Address and the personally identifiable information that you voluntarily submit may be provided to both the Time Inc. site and the third parties. Time Inc. has no control over the third parties' use of this information. 

Time Inc. sites may use reputable third parties to present or serve advertisements, including online behavioral advertisements, that you may see on the web pages and to conduct research about the advertisements. This privacy notice does not cover any use of information that such third parties may have collected from you (e.g., type of browser, operating system, domain name, day and time of visit, page(s) visited) or the methods used by the third-parties to collect that information (e.g., cookies, web beacons and clear gifs). For more information on the use of such third-parties, please [click here](http://www.timeinc.net/legal/parties.html). 

|    
  
**Cookies**  
To enhance your online experience we use cookies. Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. 

We use cookies to understand Internet usage and to improve our content, offerings and advertisements. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our site), save your password in password-protected areas and enable you to use shopping carts on our sites. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs or services. Similarly, as part of an arrangement with our business partners (including, those who present or serve the advertisements that you see on our web pages) we may also access cookies placed by others and allow others to access certain cookies placed by us. 

We may also use small pieces of code such as "web beacons" or "clear gifs" to collect anonymous and aggregate advertising metrics, such as counting page views, promotion views or advertising responses. These "web beacons" may be used to deliver cookies that conform to our cookie policy. For more information regarding cookies, please [click here](http://www.timeinc.net/legal/cookies.html). 

| back to top  
  
**Our Commitment to Security**  
We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security and correctly use the information we collect.  |    
  
**How You can Access or Correct Information**  
To inquire about personally identifiable information that this Time Inc. site has collected about you, or how to correct factual errors in such information, please email us by clicking [here](mailto:privacy@timeinc.customersvc.com).  |    
  
**Special Note for Parents**  
The site you are visiting is one of the Time Inc. general audience sites and is not intended for use by children. For more information about our online privacy practices for children's sites, consult the privacy notice at the children's site in which you are interested.  |    
  
**Changes to this Notice** This Notice may be changed by Time Inc. The revised Notice will be posted to this page so that you are aware of the information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it.  |    
  
**How to Contact Us**  
If you have any questions or concerns about the Time Inc. Privacy Notice or its implementation please contact us via email by [clicking here](mailto:privacy@timeinc.customersvc.com) or at the following address:

Time Customer Service  
Attention: Consumer Affairs  
3000 University Center Drive  
Tampa, Florida 33612-6408 

<http://www.stylefeeder.com/>

| back to top  
|  This Privacy Notice was revised 1/20/2011.
